<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- This metadata copyright 2018 Todd Warner <t0dd_at_protonmail.com> -->
<!-- https://fedoraproject.org/wiki/Packaging:AppData -->
<!-- https://www.freedesktop.org/software/appstream/docs/chap-Metadata.html -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>dash-qt.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <name>Dash Core Desktop Client</name>
  <summary>Peer-to-peer, payments-focused, fungible digital currency, protocol, and platform for payments and decentralized applications (desktop reference client)</summary>

  <description>
   <p>Dash Core reference implementation. This package provides a user-friendly(er) graphical wallet manager (dash-qt) for personal use.</p>
   <p>Dash (Digital Cash) is an open source peer-to-peer cryptocurrency with a strong focus on serving the payments industry. Dash offers a form of money
that is portable, inexpensive, divisible and fast. It can be spent securely both online and in person with minimal transaction fees. Dash offers instant
transactions (InstantSend), private transactions (PrivateSend), and operates a self-governing and self-funding model. This decentralized governance and
budgeting system makes it one of the first ever successful decentralized autonomous organizations (DAO). Dash is also a platform for innovative decentralized crypto-tech.</p>
   <p>Dash (Digital Cash) is an open source peer-to-peer cryptocurrency with a strong focus on serving as a superior means of payment. Dash offers a form of money that is portable, inexpensive, divisible and incredibly fast. It can be spent securely both online and in person with minimal transaction fees. Dash offers instant transactions (InstantSend), fungible transactions (PrivateSend), and, as a network, is self-governing and self-funding. This decentralized governance and budgeting system makes is the first ever successful decentralized autonomous organization (DAO). Dash is also a platform for innovative decentralized crypto-tech.</p>
  </description>


  <!-- <launchable type="desktop-id">dash-qt.desktop</launchable> not used for this type -->

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Dashboard</caption>
      <image>https://docs.dash.org/en/stable/_images/106329009.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>A received transaction</caption>
      <image>https://docs.dash.org/en/stable/_images/received.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>A received transaction notification</caption>
      <image>https://docs.dash.org/en/stable/_images/received-notification.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The Send tab filled out for a transaction</caption>
      <image>https://docs.dash.org/en/stable/_images/sendready.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://dash.org/</url>
  <update_contact>t0dd_at_protonmail.com</update_contact>

  <provides>
    <binary>dash-qt</binary>
  </provides>

  <releases>
    <release version="0.13.0-rc7" date="2018-12-06">
      <description>
        <p>Changelog ...coming?</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
